#### Contact

internnurse20@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/christinatheogene-bsn-rn-cnor-6b97019b (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Patient Safety
Hospitals
EMR

### Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Haitian Creole (Native or Bilingual)
French (Elementary)

# Christina Theogene, BSN, RN, CNOR

Registered Nurse-III at CHI St. Luke's Health Houston, Texas Area

# Summary

Experienced Certified Registered Nurse (CNOR) with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Medical Devices, Educational Consulting, Operating Room policy and procedures, and patient safety. Currently, possesses Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS) and Basic Life Support/CPR (BLS) skills. Strong healthcare services professional with a Graduate Certificate focused in Biomedical Informatics from The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth).

# Experience

CHI St. Luke's Health
Registered Nurse
February 2015 - Present (5 years 4 months)
Orthopedic and Neurosurgery Operating Room RN

#### **CR Bard**

Clinical Education Consultant
December 2013 - February 2015 (1 year 3 months)

Provided education and hands-on-training opportunities on genitourinary and gastrointestinal medical devices to health care professionals.

## Education

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

Graduate Certificate, Public Health Informatics · (2015 - 2017)

Florida SouthWestern State College
Bachelor of science, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse